http://dragonsfiregolf.com/privacy-policy/

Book a Tee Time
Address: 342 Concession 8 East, Flamborough, Ontario, L8N 2Z7,
Login
Forgot password?
Remember me
You can login using your social profile
[wordpress_social_login]
342 Concession 8 East, Flamborough, Ontario, L8N 2Z7
905-690-0069
Dragon's Fire Golf Club
Privacy Policy
Thank you for visiting our website. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected from our website. You can view our website and read most of the information contained herein without giving us any personal information. We do not collect personal information from users without their permission. When you use our website, you may choose to provide us with personal information for the specific purpose of inquiring into goods and services provided by DRAGON’S FIRE GOLF CLUB. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using our website, you are accepting the practices described in our privacy policy.
There are pages on our website where we request information from you in order to fulfill a request for further information. Each of these pages is clearly designed as a form with fields clearly labelled. On these forms, we clearly indicate or request information that we need to fulfill the request. We use the information we collect to fulfill your request. It is our policy not to resell the information you give us. We may, from time to time, use this information to notify you of future product availability, company events, and other related information either via e-mail, mail, or telephone. If you do not wish to receive future communications from us, please let us know via email at info[at]dragonsfiregolf.com with the subject line Unsubscribe.
There are some pages on this website that use a technology called “cookies”. Cookies are strings of text written by programs on this website to a disk file on your computer. They contain information to help us better serve you next time you return to the website. Most browsers can be configured to either notify you when websites create cookies or to disallow the creation of cookies. Refer to the documentation that came with your browser or the online help files supplied with your browser for instructions that will allow you to better control how cookies are written to your hard disk.
Read Golfer's reviews
I love coming here, it feels like a home / member course... everyone is friendly, pro shop,
starter, player assistants on the course and the drink cart team, especially Jen. The layout is fair, playable from many different tee decks, this track is always in immaculate condition.
Mike McReavy
Excellent course.
Very tough but fair.
Staff is very welcoming and knowledgeable.
I would definitely play again and reccomend to anyone.
Sean Rowland
Hard to find a more private course. Very friendly staff and great food. I wish I lived closer to this place.
Kevin Crompton
Reasonable green fees. Great course with some challenging holes. Mature trees along fairways provide some shade on the hot days. Excellent value. This is an under-rated golf course in my opinion.
DT
Well played course.. long hold ..good look to the greens.....
